the second of five meditations
the second
[music]
take care
Oh
you too
So don't think separately I and they
played like that
everyone has equal rights you
need to take care
I like to read
I'm just sowing seeds for next
time
They will definitely sign up just
Try to recognize a few words
and this
[music]
saw
and He suggested I think it's important that
He suggested half
[music]
How we didn't do Anya
because we will need
many more years to finish this time
otherwise but the story was so beautiful
so
you can read if you want but it
seems very beautiful to me [
music]
[music]
because
and there somewhere About 70 thousand temples all over the
country a lot and this is a
classic Buddhist city very
beautiful so if you have
the opportunity to visit visa programs it is
very easy to get almost a
cool place to look at this
beauty
we were there two weeks ago
[music]
[ __ ] on this one and he gives an example of
other people who
made a similar sacrifice in order to
advertise somehow
[music]
this is such a treasure  which
naturally grew a protrusion on the
head
and made as an offering a gift to
someone
this is a very famous story
They wanted to study
this by the way such a national book
Mongolia and there is a
feminine gender
which
[music]
he says
because she was in such a state
she was already on the verge of eating her
own children she had already reached
such an extreme point she would
I have not seen it written like this
approximately She was already on the verge of
eating her own
in order to at least a little
milk appeared to feed others
near her
When I become
You must become my first student You
must become
[music]
How do you teach more and more I
hope that you will teach will
this experience no
one understands anything
but continues at
first he did not want to teach It
seems to me
[music]
I thought that I want to teach a very
serious lesson is it
possible if not then
I must teach according to the article I could not I
cannot constantly teach these stories
[music]
and We started in the kitchen at someone's house we
sat around the table the
history of
toads in Minsk
the history of birth this is
[music]
very detailed
24  I don't know about the day
there, it will also be rolled out in life
If you have
[music]
I'm not saying that this is a sacrifice I'm
saying that they share their body
which
she gave your body to others Do
this not why it's not because Why did he
cut off half of his body
[music]
that his body
that everyone has different rights
I went through my three-year
removal nearby
and there was no
one there at all the
animal was very strange
and the insects were all very
strange
[music]
You can pray
for such a day to come by
the way
[music]
attempts to subscribe attention I'll now
give you an example teacher
[music]
and there was
he just found a piece of forest because he
heard a story and the Teacher said Okay, let it go of course it's
easier to meditate therefore
[music]
I tried to
do
just pray that you could achieve
such a state
When you understand that people's success through
strange rights to your time to your
attention
Slowly Very
get used to what they have
[music]
now you're interested
if you're interested
and they are always
they are always with their family
On their head, what is it called
Try to know the previous three people,
it's easier,
it's acceptable for you, don't try with
this limited body, you can't
do it, therefore
[music]
on the site, you
understand that everyone There is such a thing There is a
radical interpretation of this that there
is an equal right to your time,
just say
you because you do
because time
flies away, no matter how much you do
yoga, so many green drinks,
try to accept
this means
it makes sense to care for others,
have this
kind of
passionate sweet thinking
[music]
for example, you are growing,
we when to
go a couple more times,
this is how it happens
[music]
[music] we
spend a lot of time in order to
prepare our
tiny one, you
can go in just 10 steps, his 15
steps there and back,
what is what
and What is
controversy,
other people are, I
will not tell the girls
I can personally say that
I will not say that I have succeeded in this very
well, but I try sometimes, so
my life becomes a
miracle In general, every every work
[music]
Listen,
even if
you get
your life
[music]
Yes  this is an addiction this is a book
because you have already eaten something in the morning
drank something in the morning
what you are already on you are already somewhere some
clothes already owe someone for it
[music]
solution
your life
spent your time all your money
the best years of your life a
woman she gives
what were your affairs before
after you appeared Offer
and this body becomes
[music]
not only people
than she said
someone got pregnant our friend
already in my opinion 4 5 child
My wife says well
she just wants
[music]
mom to
get into
Tibetan training
tried to get me accepted
there
who decided Can I join the
classes
I
probably definitely won't pass
sitting
[music]
That's the word
I'm such a dad
[music]
no
were to care take
care of someone like a
child dress him feed him change
diapers wash him pay for him
because holding a child It's not just
he says
your mom
[music]
championship dog for example
I tried many brands
and two spoons are enough for
breakfast when we were studying on the course
We were so busy there was such a lot of tension
because
breakfast is with you in a small bag and it is
attached to your belt and somehow
you have time Well, literally three
minutes it’s just you stir it in water right
in the palm of your hand and it’s wonderful for
small people
with all this it’s
hard to be a farmer it’s such very
hard work I worked it’s
tough work it’s very difficult
prepared for you
[music]
helps to
separate the grain
helps
this by the way is very dangerous
bred
[music]
in order to
limitless
who put their work
into clothes that if they were ever
in Hong Kong in a helmet
[music]
someone had to wear
you can
problem sometimes
already got a lot of things because
and to some extent
because
[music]
[applause]
sale it can be bought for 1 dollar
you can get if you say
in Ukrainian
if you treat well
says that the place where
many animals often go, many people
[music]
was built by hand
and they donated their money they
gave all the money to build these
houses
Therefore, if you meet thank
them You already owe others If you live in
some house someone built a house for
you it's incredible
I got from mine
it's difficult hard work
dangerous work
[music]
there is a special person who walks and
watches if you have this maybe if
you are not by yourself this
if it were so hard you have to
[music]
this is another word
this chok here means ready ready
available
and he says just that
people already owe
a lot of time to create
[music]
a lot of work was done so that
today
what they wanted what they wanted could
somehow do it better than
me they definitely quarreled or argued with someone
but could you serve
this person better could you respect the
rights
if they have
[music]
for your time And now  we will do another
meditation and this is the one we do with the
croissant meditation,
you just take some simple thing in
your room. For example, if you have
some piece of thick or green
drink or fruit
to grow,
just start rewinding
[music]
take some food and try
rewinding, winding back,
then we will spin deeper and deeper. There is a
very beautiful meditation,
it is called rewinding back,
we just rewind
[music]
then I want to go back to
this again, the
person who planted it, he used
this garden, who made it. Before that, and then
another
fruit, which is
accounting work,
thousands work as an accountant, so
think about some
or here we are all Diamond on the Mountain,
picked out something, juice or some
piece of bread or a little
[music]
Imagine what he or she looks like
now. Imagine where they got this food.
Maybe in some store.
Imagine all these people who
work in this store that
puts all these products on the shelves
and worked all day.
It delivered vegetables, fruits, farms,
tomato,
I worked,
did this work when  he is a student in
college this is hard work
this collected
[music]
this is
gone
we already owe them
time our body and they have the right
to ours they
already have the right even to our body
for what we do with it
and the very thought to thank that
they already have the right to my
time
it also has a history
and this is the second meditation that I want to
practice today
myself
on it
Yes it is where the Source
I will hear
I want you to mentally track
which
brought you to this point in time
your mind today is considering the possibility
that other people already have the right to
own
some part of our time if we
respect
that everyone has the right in this world
then all these people already have
where did this idea come from in the first place
who said that they have equals about you
Why do I hear this now I heard on
this Rome well
and I thought that
I want to listen to this course I want to
know more
and what are you thinking about
I thought what good I can do with
my life
where is this thought
I think
that when I was in college I heard
I thought
and my mom and dad were talking about how it would be
nice for me to study in college
No I remember  What I thought
about history and the whole world about how I
studied at school I remember these thoughts I remember
about what I felt when I went to
first grade
especially about what went wrong at school
I remember how I felt you
feeling I remember that I was curious about what
books are such people what
they will teach I remember
I remember such the first day
I remember
What they talked about
[music]
I want to do
two meditations The first
is physical
just choose what you have already eaten or what you are
wearing or what you were the
dream in which you are
and just trace it back and to all these
people who produced the material
that passed on knowledge about how
to build a house for 50 thousand years and
thank
gratitude